A lot can happen on the road to nowhere.
Wild Hogs is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Walt Becker.
Restless and ready for an adventure, four suburban bikers leave the
safety of their subdivision and head out on the open road.
But complications ensue when they cross paths with an intimidating
band of New Mexico bikers known as the Del Fuegos.
Doug Madsen, played by Tim Allen.
Woody Stevens, played by John Travolta.
Bobby Davis, played by Martin Lawrence.
Dudley Frank, played by William H. Macy.
Jack, played by Ray Liotta.
Red, played by Kevin Durand.
Wild Hogs is a 2007 American biker road comedy film written by Brad Copeland, directed by Walt
Becker and starring Tim Allen, John Travolta, Martin Lawrence and William H.
It was released nationwide in the United States and Canada on March 2,
2007 to negative reviews but was a box office success.
It was the last Touchstone Pictures film to be distributed by Buena Vista Pictures Distribution, after
Disney retired the Buena Vista moniker across their company's divisions in the same year.
The theatrical distribution label became Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures.
The film explores themes of small town, midlife crisis, road
trip, slapstick comedy, politically incorrect.
The tone is lighthearted.